http://terralindavet.com/legal/

4230 Redwood Hwy CA, San Rafael, CA 94903
M-F:
7 a.m.–7 p.m.
SAT: 8 a.m.–4 p.m.
SUN: Closed
P: (415) 479-8535
F: (866) 722-1183
After-Hour Emergencies: Contact Pet Emergency & Specialty Center of Marin: (415) 456-7372
Terra Linda Veterinary Hospital»Legal
PRIVACY POLICY:
This practice is required to provide our clients with notice of our privacy practices with respect to protected personal information collected from this website.
Consent
By using this website, you consent to understanding and accepting the terms listed in this privacy policy. We reserve the right to update, amend, or change this Privacy Policy at any time to conform to new laws and regulations or changes in business standards. This privacy policy does not extend to any third-party websites that link to or from our website and we are not responsible for any of the content on those websites. Those websites have their own privacy policies and it is recommended that users read through them before providing any information to the website owner.
Information Security
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. All forms have 256 bit encryption to securely transmit information.
We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.
Our privacy policy does not cover content that is transmitted via email to our office. Email does not have the same encryption and security protocols and should not be used to transmit sensitive information.
Log Information
When you use our website, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.
Cookies enable us to customize your browsing experience and speed up website load times. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies at any time. If you decline cookies, you do not have access to the benefits of a custom web browsing experience.
Information Sharing
Our monthly newsletter service sends monthly newsletters with relevant information to the topic of interest. Your email will not be sold, rented or leased to a third-party. You may remove your name from the newsletter list at any time by following the removal instructions at the bottom of any newsletter sent.
Social Media Policy
We are not responsible for any information collected by social networks on which we maintain a social media presence. These include, but are not limited to, Facebook, Google, Twitter, Instagram, Pinterest, and LinkedIn. Each social network has its own privacy policy and it should be read before creating an account on the network. We are not responsible for any marketing or re-targeting performed by a social network after you have visited our pages
Terms
This Practice requires that all users of this website agree to comply with the Terms of Use of this website. Users who do not agree with these Terms and Conditions must leave the website.
Information on this Website
Though The Website Providers have taken reasonable steps to include accurate information and content on this website, The Website Providers are not responsible for any error or inaccurate information provided herein. The information provided on this website is provided “as is” and is free from any guarantee, warrantee, or claim of usability. Users of this website use the information provided here at their own risk, and The Website Providers are not responsible for any consequence arising from the use of such information. Furthermore, The Website Providers are not responsible for the content of websites linked from this website, which are the responsibility of the respective website operators. The Website Providers cannot attest to the accuracy or fitness of any claim or item of information in any website linked from this website.
Intellectual Property
The information provided here in this website may not be copied, reused/modified, stored or retained except for review. Any other copying, reuse/modification, storage or publication of any kind must be approved in writing by The Website Providers prior to such use. All trademarks and copyrighted information contained on the Website are the property of their respective owners.
Modification
The Website Providers reserve the right to add, delete, or modify any provision of its Terms of Use at any time without notice.
